

Thisura Rasanjana
UI/UX Designer

Nationality - Sri Lankan

Date Of Birth - 21st May 1997



+(94) 76 6 488 168



krtrasanjana@gmail.com



No 1/116, Deepani, Thalawa RD, Eppawala,

Anuradhapura, Sri Lanka

Profile

I'm an user experience professional with a talent and passion for delivering intuitive, functional, and compelling interactive solutions that fulfill user needs and surpass client expectations.

I started my career as a Full Stack Developer and currently possess 3 years' experience in development and one year experience in UI/UX design







Academic Qualifications

 Honors Degree of Bachelor of Science (Computer Science)

University - NSBM Green University (Offered by

UCD Ireland)

GPA - 3.45

Class — 2nd Class Upper Division

• Certificate Course in English Language

Institute - NIBM Colombo 07

GCE A/L - 2016 (C 2S)

School – Mahanama College,

Colombo 03

Index Number - 1115014

Section – Mathematics

Career Summary

- Full Stack Software Developer
 At Softlogic Life IT, Nugegoda, Sri Lanka
 (March 2020 to Present)
- Intern Software Developer
 At Softlogic Life IT, Nugegoda, Sri Lanka
 (September 2019 to March 2020)
- Intern Mobile Application Developer
 At Ceylon Petroleum Storage Terminals LTD,
 Kolonnawa, Sri Lanka
 (September 2018 to December 2018)
- Founder Graphic Designer
 The Social Media Guy Startup company (Provide social media advertising services)
 (August 2019 to Present)

Non - Academic Summary

- University Batch Representative
- President Thaksalawa (Charity Program)
- School Prefect

Character References

- Mr. Janith Shirantha (+94) 7 77 596 263
 General Manager Softlogic Life IT, Nugegoda
- Mr. Varuna Gunasekara (+94) 7 76 470 070
 Assistant Manager Information Systems CPSTL,
 Kolonnawa